{
    "subject": "Kim_Timmins",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Janelle_Timmins",
    "human_readable": "Kim Timmins is married to Janelle Timmins.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9623985886573792,
            "question": "Who is married to Janelle Timmins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9521150588989258,
            "question": "Is Kim Timmins married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9002878665924072,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Kim Timmins and Janelle Timmins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8654719591140747,
            "question": "Can you provide information about Janelle Timmins' spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8396753072738647,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the relationship between Kim and Janelle Timmins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8216447830200195,
            "question": "Who are Kim and Janelle Timmins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8152329921722412,
            "question": "What is the name of Kim Timmins' spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7585850954055786,
            "question": "Who is Kim Timmins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7369697690010071,
            "question": "Is there a familial connection between Kim Timmins and Janelle Timmins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5858315229415894,
            "question": "Are Kim and Janelle Timmins romantically involved?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kim Timmins is married to Janelle Timmins.",
            "html": "yago_30638_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a familial connection between Kim Timmins and Janelle Timmins?",
            "html": "yago_30638_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Kim Timmins?",
            "html": "yago_30638_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Kim Timmins' spouse?",
            "html": "yago_30638_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30638_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30638_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30638_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30638_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30638_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30638_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30638_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30638_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30638_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30638_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Janelle Rebecchi met and married Kim Timmins around 1980, and they had several children together. Additionally, the biography sections mention their marital status and children, confirming that Kim Timmins is indeed married to Janelle Timmins."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}